ILGWU Local 62 Correspondence 5780/022
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILGWU Local 62 Correspondence
1913-1980
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILGWU Local 62
5780/022
9 cubic feet
9 linear ft.
Articles, correspondence, reports, photographs.
The Local 62 correspondence consists primarily of letters of Samuel Shore and Louis Stulberg, the managers of the Local during much of the period. There are also articles, photographs, reports, and other materials in the collection. These items primarily document the activities and concerns of the Local's leadership from the depression years through the 1960s.
3708646
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, September 11, 2002
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 02, 2019
Biographical / Historical
The International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union was once one of the largest labor unions in the United States founded in 1900 by local union delegates representing about 2,000 members in cities in the northeastern United States. It was one of the first U.S. Unions to have a membership consisting of mostly females, and it played a key role in the labor history of the 1920s and 1930s. The union is generally referred to as the "ILGWU" or the "ILG". The ILGWU grew in geographical scope, membership size, and political influence to become one of the most powerful forces in American organized labor by mid-century. Representing workers in the women's garment industry, the ILGWU worked to improve working and living conditions of its members through collective bargaining agreements, training programs, health care facilities, cooperative housing, educational opportunities, and other efforts. The ILGWU merged with the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union in 1995 to form the Union of Needle trades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE). UNITE merged with the Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union (HERE) in 2004 to create a new union known as UNITE HERE. The two unions that formed UNITE in 1995 represented only 250,000 workers between them, down from the ILGWU's peak membership of 450,000 in 1969.
Biographical / Historical
The White Goods Workers' Union Local 62, also known as the Underwear and White Goods Workers Union, was chartered in 1909, but was not fully organized until 1913. Rose Schneiderman and the Women's Trade Union League assisted with the early organizing efforts of the White Goods Workers. These workers consisted mainly of young immigrant girls. Early leaders of the local included Samuel Shore. On March 1913, 15,000 workers went on strike against the sweatshop conditions. A six week strike ensued in which many of the girls on the picket lines were attacked and arrested. Gains won included a 54 hour week, no Sunday, sanitary conditions and an 18 cent an hour minimum wage. This strike made the local.
The local and its workers were originally called white goods workers as they manufactured camisoles, chemises, cambric drawers with lace ruffles and drawstrings, and corset covers. Through the years, styles changed and production shifted to panties and slips. In the 1960s, the local became the Undergarment and Negligee Workers' Union Local 62.
Scope and Contents
The Local 62 correspondence consists primarily of letters of Samuel Shore and Louis Stulberg, the managers of the Local during much of the period. These items primarily document the activities and concerns of the Local's leadership from the depression years through the 1960s. The bulk of the material deals with Local administrative matters, benefits, garment manufacturers, other ILGWU departments and locals, political activity (at both the national and local level), relations with other unions, union organizing, wages, and working conditions in the shops. It is mostly restricted to New York City. In addition, there is some personal correspondence of both Shore and Stulberg.
The first series contains the correspondence of Samuel Shore, manager of Local 62. Topics discussed include parade and demonstration fliers, calls for local elections and polling place locations, final decisions of cases that went to arbitration with the Impartial Chairman, and correspondence with various ILGWU Departments (Education, Health and Welfare), presidents office (David Dubinsky), and Joint Boards and District Councils and Locals. Mixed in are meeting minutes for committees. There are also records documenting the social causes the local was involved with, particularly the children "adopted" by the local in Europe in which they supported and sent money as well as exchanging letters with the children. Information on individual shops can be found in the reports from the Business Agents in which they report on cases, disputes, and conditions. Reports are identified by Business Agent. Historical information can be found in the articles and speeches of Shore. There are photographs of the Local 62 outing to Unity House.
The second series contains the correspondence of Louis Stulberg, who became manager of Local 62 in 1947. Though, much of his correspondence and work as manager can be found in the first series though. Correspondence occurs with organizations and associations, departments (Education, Auditing, Health and Welfare, Legal, Research, Management Engineering, Union Label ), and includes administrative information (dues, finances, elections). There is much correspondence with firms, and the files are identified by shop name, these often include agreements, arbitration cases. Some of the material contained in the files are from when Stulberg was no longer with the local.
The third series consists of files from Gerel Rubien, who was the Education Director. Of particular importance is the collection of "Our Union" newsletters and scrapbooks that contain clippings on the garment industry, and more particularly the lingerie and negligee industry and white goods, some from as early as the 1913 strike, as well as the 1933 strike, early agreements, a photograph from 1921, and a collection of speeches.
Individual correspondents represented in the collection include: David Dubinsky; Jacob Javits; Elias Lieberman; Eleanor Roosevelt; Franklin D. Roosevelt; Rose Schneiderman; Matthew Schoenwald; and Norman Thomas. Organizations include: the AFL-CIO; the American Labor Party; Histadrut; the Jewish Daily Forward; the Jewish Labor Committee; the Liberal Party of New York; the Negro Labor Committee; the National Recovery Administration; the Rand School of Social Research; and the Socialist Party.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5780: ILGWU records 5780/021: ILGWU Local 62 Records 5780/074: ILGWU Mary Goff Schuster Papers 5780/079: ILGWU Local 62 Managers' Correspondence 5780/089: ILGWU Local 62-32 Agreements
Arrangement
Series I: Samuel Shore correspondence, 1930-1946.
Series II: Louis Stulberg correspondence, 1947-1956.
Series III: Gerol Rubien files, 1921-1976
Labor unions -- Officials and employees; Lingerie industry -- New York (State) -- New York; Lingerie industry -- Employees -- New York (State) -- New York; Labor union locals.; Wages -- Underwear industry -- New York (State) -- New York; Women's clothing industry -- New York (State) -- New York; Work environment -- New York (State) -- New York; New York (State) -- Politics and government -- 20th century; United States--Politics and government--20th century.; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union; Dubinsky, David, 1892-1982.; Javits, Jacob K.(Jacob Koppel), 1904-1986.; Lieberman, Elias, b. 1888-; Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1884-1962.; Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Franklin Delano), 1882-1945.; Schneiderman, Rose, 1882-1972.; Schoenwald, Matthew.; Shore, Samuel.; Stulberg, Louis, 1901-1977.; Thomas, Norman, 1884-1968.; AFL-CIO; American Labor Party; Histadrut ha-kelalit shel ha-'ovdim be-Erets-Yisra'el; Jewish Labor Committee (U.S.); Liberal Party of New York State; Negro Labor Committee; Rand School of Social Science; United States. National Recovery Administration; Forv?ert?s (New York, N.Y.)
3708646
- Series Series I: Samuel Shore correspondence, 1930-1946.
  - General Correspondence. A, 1944-1953 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence. Agreements w. firms and conference w. Negligee-Lingerie Assoc. (1941), 1931-1937 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence. American Labor Party, 1936-1944 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence. B, 1943-1953 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence. C, 1935-1949 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence. Circulars, 1930-1953 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Scope and Contents
    Incl. other locals.
  - General Correspondence. D, 1937-1953 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence. East River Housing Corp., 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Incl. minutes of meetings.
  - General Correspondence. Educational Dept., 1936 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Report on activities.
  - General Correspondence. Elections, 1937-1947 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Incl. minutes of election & Objection Committee, March 1937.
  - General Correspondence. Epstein, Melech, Book Fund, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - General Correspondence. F, 1942-1949 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - General Correspondence. Freedom House, 1941-1955 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - General Correspondence. G, 1936-1948 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - General Correspondence. H, 1941-1952 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - General Correspondence. Histadrut-Nat'l. Labor Comm. for Palestine, 1946-1953 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - General Correspondence. I, 1945-1947 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - General Correspondence. Impartial Chairman decisions, 1935-1952 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
    Incl. decisions by George J. Mintzer.
  - General Correspondence. Infantile Paralysis Fund, 1945-1953 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - General Correspondence. Int'l. Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, General Office, 1935-1955 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Corres. w. David Dubinsky.
  - General Correspondence. ILGWU, Education Dept., 1934-1953 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence. ILGWU, Health and Welfare Dept., 1948-1953 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence. Javits, Jacob K., 1947-1952 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence. Jewish Daily Forward, 1935-1953 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Incl. Local greetings & articles.
  - General Correspondence. Jewish Labor Committee, 1944-1953 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence. Joint Boards and District Councils, 1952-1956 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Incl. correspondence. w. John S. Martin & E. T. Kehrer.
  - General Correspondence. Jt. Bds. and Dist. Councils, 1936-1951 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Incl. Los Angeles Cloak Jt. Bd.
  - General Correspondence. K, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence. L, 1935-1953 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence. Labor Day Ads, 1944-1950 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    (see also Jewish Daily Forward)
  - General Correspondence. Labor Stage, 1935-1937 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - General Correspondence. Langer, Judith, Trust Fund, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - General Correspondence. Liberal Party, 1944-1955 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence. Lieberman, Elias, 1940-1955 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Incl. cases.
  - General Correspondence. Locals, 1936-1952 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence. M, 1935-1952 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence. Minutes, Organizing Comm., 1927 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence. Minutes, Shop Chair ladies and Membership Meetings, 1935-1948 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence. N, 1932-1952 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Incl. Negro Labor Committee.
  - General Correspondence. National Recovery Administration, 1934-1935 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Aug. 1934-July 1935. Corres., minutes of Code Authority for Undergarment & Negligee Industry.
  - General Correspondence. National Recovery Administration, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Jan.-July
  - General Correspondence. Organization for Rehabilitation Through Training in Industry and Agriculture (ORT), 1936-1946 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence. Overseas Children, 1939-1948 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Corres. bet. Stulberg & "adopted" European war orphans.
  - General Correspondence. Overseas Children, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 1-2)
  - General Correspondence. Overseas Children, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence. Overseas Children, 1951-1952 (Box 4, Folder 4a-4b)
    Incl. correspondence. w. Jewish Labor Comm.
  - General Correspondence. P-Q, 1935-1944 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence. Politics, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Reports on Local activities.
  - General Correspondence. Pope, Generoso, 1940-1948 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence. Puerto Rico, 1935 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence. R, 1934-1947 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence. Rand School of Social Research, 1936-1944 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence. Reports, Advisory Board, 1935-1961 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - General Correspondence. Reports, Business Agents, 1935 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - General Correspondence. Reports, Business Agents, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    May-Dec.
  - General Correspondence. Reports, Business Agents, 1936-1938 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Jan. 1936-April 1938
  - General Correspondence. Reports, Business Agents, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    June-Nov.
  - General Correspondence. Reports, Business Agents, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Jan-May
  - General Correspondence. Reports, Business Agents, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence. Reports, Business Agents, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Jan.-May
  - General Correspondence. Reports, Business Agents, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence. Reports, Business Agents, 1945-1946 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence. Reports to Convention, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence. Reports to General Executive Board, 1940-1955 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence. Reports, Misc., 1941-1942 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence. Roosevelt, Franklin D., 1934-1943 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence. S, 1939-1952 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence. Sanatoriums, 1935-1955 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence. Service Men (Armed Forces), 1943-1945 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence. Shop Chairladies' Luncheon, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    Incl. Stulberg Speech.
  - General Correspondence. Shore, Samuel, 1930-1949 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    Articles, speeches & notes.
  - General Correspondence. Shore, Samuel, 1944-1946 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Personal matters.
  - General Correspondence. Sick Benefits Fund, 1937-1946 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Incl. constitutions, by-laws.
  - General Correspondence. Statements, Releases, Resolutions, 1934-1952 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence. Stulberg, Louis, 1948-1952 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Articles & speeches.
  - General Correspondence. Stulberg, Louis, 1947-1955 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    Personal.
  - General Correspondence. T, 1934-1939 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence. Treasury Department, 1944-1945 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence. Trade Associations, 1934-1951 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    Incl. correspondence., reports, minutes of Lingerie Mfrs. Assoc. & Negligee Mfrs. Assoc.
  - General Correspondence. U, 1941-1944 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence. Union Health Center, 1940-1944 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence. Unions, 1934-1953 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - General Correspondence. Unity House, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    Outing photographs.
  - General Correspondence. Universities, 1945-1946 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    Corres. w. members' (Mabel Durham) schooling at Harvard Univ.
  - General Correspondence. Vacation Fund, 1942-1947 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    Rules & regulations, reports.
  - General Correspondence. W, 1941-1955 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - General Correspondence. War Labor Board, 1943-1944 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - General Correspondence. Yiddish Writers Union, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - General Correspondence. Zukunft, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Series Series II: Louis Stulberg correspondence, 1947-1956.
  - General Correspondence. Advisory Board, Local 62, 1933-1934 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Incl. joint meetings of the Educational Committee and the Advisory Board.
  - General Correspondence. American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Corres. w. Maida Springer, Representative, International Affairs Dept. re ILGWU involvement in African garment workers' trainee program.
  - General Correspondence. Americans for Democratic Action, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence. Association of Catholic Trade Unionists, 1957-1961 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Complaints from ILGWU workers to Association.
  - General Correspondence. Brassiere shops, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    List of settled shops. Incl. approximate number of workers, names of shop chairladies & assistant chairladies.
  - General Correspondence. Brookwood Labor College, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence. Business Agent Reports, 1954-1962 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence. Celebrations, 1947-1961 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    Louis Stulberg birthdays and chairladies luncheon.
  - General Correspondence. Census of membership, 1957-1963 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence. Central Labor Council, AFL-CIO, New York City, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    Corres. re workers' complaints.
  - General Correspondence. Davis, William, 1922 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    Report of meeting in the matter of the resignation and dismissal of William Davis, former manager of Local 62, November 2, 1922.
  - General Correspondence. The Day, 1954-1960 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    Greetings.
  - General Correspondence. El Diario, 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - General Correspondence. Dues, 1933-1958 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    Incl. correspondence. re arrears, 1933-34; analysis of dues and incoming members, 1956-58.
  - General Correspondence. Educational Dept., 1933-1964 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    Corres. and notices, questionnaires, program for winter 1933.
  - General Correspondence. Elections, Local 62, 1913-1953 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    Incl. sample ballots, lists of candidates, election tallies, reports of election-objection committee.
  - General Correspondence. Executive Board, Local 62, 1930-1968 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - General Correspondence. F, 1934-1963 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - General Correspondence. Financial reports, 1959-1962 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - General Correspondence. Fire Department, New York City, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    Corres. re breakdown of fire warden program.
  - General Correspondence. Firms, A and G Mfg. Inc., 1963 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - General Correspondence. Firms, A and S Novelty Co., 1957-1961 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - General Correspondence. Firms, Arrow Knitting Mills, 1957-1961 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - General Correspondence. Firms, Aurora Undergarment, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - General Correspondence. Firms, Campus Girl Inc., 1964 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - General Correspondence. Firms, Cotton Art, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - General Correspondence. Firms, Lucette Pajama Co., Inc., 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - General Correspondence. Firms, Madest Undergarment Co, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - General Correspondence. Firms, Max C. Schrank Co., 1934 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    Corres. w. Donald Pratt, City Editor, Women's Wear Daily.
  - General Correspondence. Firms, Misc., 1934-1963 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    Including Management Engineering Dept. reports on Rhine Undergarment Co & Tri J & S Co
  - General Correspondence. Firms, Monarch Undergarment Co., 1958 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - General Correspondence. Firms, P. Gusson, 1954-1957 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - General Correspondence. Firms, Q.T. Knitwear, 1957-1960 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Incl. report on meetings with El Diario staff re complaints received by newspaper from ILGWU members.
  - General Correspondence. Firms, Ruther Undergarment Co., 1954 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence. Firms, S. Haber and Son, 1956-1957 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence. Firms, Siren Silk Undergarment Co., Inc., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence. Firms; Skylon Corp., 1957 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence. Firms, Sonjay Mills, Inc., 1958-1963 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence. Firms, South Jersey Underwear Co., 1959 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence. Firms, Style Undies, 1957-1958 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence. Firms, Sure-Fit Mfg. Co., 1959 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence. Firms, Trebor Knitting Mills, Inc., 1960 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence. Firms, Well Made Strap and Novelty Co., 1954 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - General Correspondence. Firms, Yolande Corp., 1957-1963 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - General Correspondence. Firms, Youth form, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    Corres. re work sent to non-union contractor (Newport Mfg. Co.).
  - General Correspondence. Four Freedoms Hotel, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - General Correspondence. Freedom House, Inc., 1961 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - General Correspondence. Freie Arbeiter Stimme, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Letters re Emma Goldman reception meeting.
  - General Correspondence. General Executive Board, reports to, 1954-1955 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Louis Stulberg reports on Local 62 and on underwear and negligee industry.
  - General Correspondence. Health, Welfare and Vacation Fund, 1948-1962 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Incl. By-Laws, Rules and Regulations of the Undergarment and Negligee Workers' Union, Local 62, and minutes, Health and Welfare Benefits Committee meetings, 195
  - General Correspondence. High School of Fashion Industries, 1957-1962 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - General Correspondence. Histadrut, (American Trade Union Council for), 1962 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - General Correspondence. Housewarming, Local 62, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - General Correspondence. Il Progresso Italo-Americano, 1957-1960 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - General Correspondence. I.L.G.W.U. General Office, President's Office, 1954-1961 (Box 9, Folder 23-24)
  - General Correspondence. I.L.G.W.U. Executive Vice-President, Louis Stulberg, 1956-1958 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Incl. worker's complaint.
  - General Correspondence. I.L.G.W.U. General Secretary Treasurer, Louis Stulberg, 1959-1962 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - General Correspondence. I.L.G.W.U., Auditing Department, 1934-1954 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - General Correspondence. I.L.G.W.U. campaign committees, 1954-1962 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - General Correspondence. I.L.G.W.U. conventions, 1956-1965 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    Incl. 1962 resolutions submitted by Local 62.
  - General Correspondence. I.L.G.W.U. Eastern Out-Of-Town Dept., 1954-1957 (Box 9, Folder 30-31)
  - General Correspondence. I.L.G.W.U. Eastern Region, 1960-1962 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - General Correspondence. I.L.G.W.U. Educational Dept., 1933-1960 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - General Correspondence. I.L.G.W.U. Health and Welfare Dept., 1956-1961 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence. I.L.G.W.U. Legal Dept., 1958 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence. I.L.G.W.U. locals, 1959-1962 (Box 10, Folder 3-4)
    Corres. w. Local 89 & Local 600 (Puerto Rico).
  - General Correspondence. I.L.G.W.U. Management Engineering Dept., 1954-1959 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence. I.L.G.W.U. Northeast Dept., 1954-1962 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence. I.L.G.W.U. Research Dept., 1955-1962 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence. I.L.G.W.U. Southeast Region, 1956-1961 (Box 10, Folder 8-9)